michigandaily.com 2006-10-18

# Michigan Daily

## Privacy Commitment

### Overview

College Publisher, the operator of this site and custodian of the information gathered herein, in conjunction with our affiliated Media Partners and Sponsors, commits to ensuring that no information will be provided to others in any form that will personally identify you, unless you have authorized us to do so. Neither College Publisher nor our Media Partners will sell, share, or rent any personally identifiable information collected from you with other third parties unless you have authorized us to do so.

College Publisher, on behalf of our affiliated Media Partners & Sponsors may ask visitors for information that will help us improve our ability to present meaningful, tailored news, information, services and products to each reader, member, subscriber or registered user. We regard the privacy and security of such information as a critical component of the services that we offer. The following explains the information gathering and dissemination practices used at our Web sites.

The more information you, the reader, member, subscriber or registered user provides regarding your name, contact details, interests, concerns and personal details, the more effective our sites can be at offering news, information, products, services and/or advice that meet your needs. Any personal information you share through this site will be used solely to provide an efficient, focused experience, and to deliver information and services that are appropriate for your unique situation.

### Information Collection and Use

College Publisher is the operator and custodian of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. Our sites collect information from users at several different points on our website.

### Registration

College Publisher operates and provides email and database services that enable users to receive information, news, content and services that they are interested in receiving. Our registration forms may require you to give us your name, email address, college or university name, and affiliation and/or class year and/or certain contact or demographic information (“Registration Data”). We use Registration Data if it is necessary for us to contact a user, and to send you information, service enhancements, complementary goods and services, and/or promotional materials that you have agreed to receive from our media Partners, Advertisers, & Sponsors (“Partners, Advertisers & Sponsors”). If you choose to stop receiving future communications, please see the Opt-Out/Unsubscribe section below.

### Contests, Surveys & Referrals

From time to time, we run contests and surveys on our site in which we may ask contestants for personal information and/or referrals. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), demographic information (such as zip code, age level) and preference information (interest in travel, money, etc). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site. If a user elects to use our referral service for informing a referee about our site or services, we may ask them for certain contact details for the referee.

### Online Actions

Demographic and profile data may also be collected from time to time at our Web site.

Generally, this information is collected through “traffic data” and may entail the use of cookies, IP addresses or other numeric codes used to identify a computer. We use this information to further tailor your experience at our site, and to narrow the information, content, products and or services we think you might be interested in.

· IP Addresses – We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is also used to help identify you and to gather broad demographic information.

· Cookies – Cookies are pieces of information that a Web site transfers to your computer’s hard disk for record-keeping purposes. Cookies in and of themselves do not personally identify users, although they do identify a user’s computer. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. If you prefer, you can set your browser to notify you each time a cookie is received or to refuse all cookies. However, you may not be able to take full advantage of our Web sites if you do so. For example, we use cookies to save your password so that (if you choose) you do not have to reenter it each time you visit our Web sites. Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies.

### Classifieds, Orders and other ecommerce transactions

For ecommerce transactions we request information from the user as per the ordering process. During this process a user must provide relevant contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fulfill user requirements. If we have trouble processing an order, this contact information is used to get in touch with the user.

### Sharing of Information

We will only disclose personal data about you to the extent described in this Privacy Statement.

No personally identifiable information will be shared with our Partners, Advertisers & Sponsors unless you have agreed to allow us to share such information (although you may separately provide them such information). Some of your information may be shared on an aggregate basis only, as a part of a larger set of statistics (for example, that a certain percentage of our members are male), but that information will not be sufficient to permit the recipient to identify you.

Should you at some time request through our site something that requires shipping to you, we may be required to provide your personal details to outside shipping companies, credit card processing companies and other third parties to enable your request to be processed. These companies, to our knowledge, do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes.

We sometimes contract with other companies to provide specific services on our behalf. When the user signs up for these services, we will share names, or other contact information that is necessary for the third party service provider to deliver these services. These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services.

As we continue to develop our services, we might sell or buy companies or assets. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets. Also, in the unlikely event that we or substantially all of our assets are acquired, customer information will of course be one of the transferred assets.

Except as set forth in the Terms of Service and this Privacy Statement, we will not willfully disclose personal data about you to any third party without first receiving your permission.

### Security

Information collected by us is stored in secure operating environments that are not accessible by the public. Our Web sites have security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of the information under our control. When capturing credit card information, we use Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology, an encryption technology that works with Netscape Navigator and Communicator (versions 2.0 and above), Microsoft Internet Explorer (versions 3.0 and above) and AOL (AOL 3.0 and above) so that unauthorized parties cannot read the information you send over the Internet. Credit card information is not stored on our servers, it is simply passed through to the processing financial institution via SSL.

### Other Web Sites and Links

We sometimes provide links to other Web sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these other Web sites.

Additionally, if you make a purchase from a merchant listed on or linked to the our service, any information that you give, such as your credit card number and contact information, is provided to those merchants. These merchants have separate privacy and data collection practices and we assume no responsibility or liability for these independent policies. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our sites and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by us

### Public Forums

Our services may enable members to make certain information publicly available on the Web sites. Be advised that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

### Corrections and Updates

Members may correct, update or edit information that they have previously provided by sending an email to feedback@collegepublisher.com (or written mail to the address below), including your name, email address and the information to be changed.

### Opt-Out/Unsubscribe

Our Web site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us at the point where we request information about the visitor. You may elect to avoid future communications from us by sending an email to feedback@collegepublisher.com (or written mail to the address below), including your name, email address, and specifics of your request.

In addition, every email that is sent to your account will contain instructions and links to allow you to unsubscribe from the specific service.

After you opt-out, we may still need to send you information about the service or your account under urgent circumstances, but we will not send you unsolicited communications.

### Notification of Changes

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our websites so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected. 

If you choose to visit our sites, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Notice and our Conditions of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of the law of the state of Massachusetts. 

### Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Statement, the practices of our Web sites or your dealings with our Web sites, please contact:

  * College Publisher
  * 100 City Hall Plaza
  * Level 2
  * Boston, MA 02108

Email: feedback@collegepublisher.com  
Phone: (617) 248-9880  
Fax: (617) 248-8747
